Finding aid for the Bonnie Cashin Collection of Fashion, Theater, and Film Costume Design LSC.0440
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Personal Papers, 1937 - 2000; 40 oversize boxes (323 folders)
  - Collected Poems and Essays, ca. 1960s - 1980s; 1 oversize box
    - Essays collected by Cashin:Norman Cousins "Anatomy of an Illness"; Max Ehrmann excerpts from "Desiderata"; Edgar Mitchell "The Perennial Puzzle of Untapped Potentials"; Brodemas untitled speech; Solomon E. Asch "Opinions and Social Pressure"; con't., ca. 1960s - 1980s (dates collected); 30 pag
      James H. Austin-"The Roots of Serendipity'; Keith Henderson-"Think Tanks Spread Free-Market Ideas Worldwide"
    - Speeches collected by Cashin: Dorothy Shaver, president of Lord & Taylor; Albert Einstein, acceptance speech; Bernice Fitz-Gibbon, Home Fashions League Luncheon; David Schoenbrun, CBS News Paris correspondent; con't., ca. 1960s - 1980s (dates collected); 41 pages (Box 251, Folder 3)
      Estelle Hamburge, "Fabric Report and a Few Extra Words"; Ed Stone, "The American Way of Life"; Sidney Berkowitz, "Dear Harry"; Pietro Nenni, Vice-Premier of Italy
    - Essays collected by Cashin: Abraham Lincoln The Gettysburg Address; no author "What Are The Arts Telling Us About Our World?"; Ben Shahn no title; Edgar Kaufmann Jr. "A Profitable Art"; Louis I. Kahn "Architecture and Human Agreement"; con't., ca. 1960s - 1980s (dates collected); 25 pages (Box 251, Folder 4)
    - Speech by Ettore Sottsass., ca. 1960s - 1980s (dates collected); 27 pages (Box 251, Folder 5)
    - Raymond Moriyama "Can Your Life Become a Work of Art?" F.B. Watts Memorial Lecture, Scarborough College., ca. 1960s - 1980s (dates collected); 19 pages (Box 251, Folder 6)
    - Quotes and writings regarding religion collected by Cashin., ca. 1964 - 1968; 6 pages (Box 251, Folder 7)
  - Collected Art, ca. 1925 - 1980; 4 folders
    This subseries contains drawings and paintings given to or collected by Bonnie Cashin.
    - Portraits of Cashin by various artists., 1925, 1960s and 1970; 9 portraits (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Drawings, paintings, and images collected by Cashin., ca. 1940 - 1970; 42 pages (Box 286, Folder 2)
    - Paintings by E. Nicholson., 1945; 2 paintings (Box 286, Folder 3)
    - Children's art, including works by Cashin's niece and nephew., ca. 1960 - 1980; 29 works of art (Box 286, Folder 4)
    - Mats used for exhibition of Cashin's works on paper., 2003; 12 archival mats (Box 287, Folder 1)
- Rainwear Designs, ca. 1951 - 1963; 3 oversize boxes and 3 folders
  This series contains Bonnie Cashin's record of her raincoat design contracts. The series largely consists of Cashin's design illustrations. The series is subdivided by manufacturer: Norman Zeiler, Siggy Raincoat / Mainstreet, Harris Raincoat Co. / March and Mendl, and Modelia. All illustrations and writings by Bonnie Cashin contained in this series are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
  - Norman Zeiler, ca. 1951 - 1952; 4 folders
    This subseries contains Bonnie Cashin's illustrations of rainwear designs for manufacturer Norman Zeiler. All materials contained in this subseries are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
    - Coat design illustrations by Cashin for Norman Zeiler. Folder 1 of 2., ca. 1951; 6 illustrations (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Photostats of coat design illustrations by Cashin for Norman Zeiler. Folder 2 of 2., ca. 1951; 8 illustrations (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's illustrations of raincoat designs for Norman Zeiler (reduced copies)., ca. 1951; 6 illustrations (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's illustrations of coat designs for Norman Zeiler, with swatches., 1952; 5 illustrations (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Siggy Raincoat Co. / Mainstreet, 1950 - 1953; 2 folders
    This subseries contains documentation of Bonnie Cashin's rainwear designs for manufacturer Siggy Raincoat Co., a division of Mainstreet. This subseries contains one sketchbook in very fragile condition as well as Cashin's design illustrations and photographs featuring her designs. All illustrations by Bonnie Cashin contained in this subseries are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
    - Sketches and photographs of Cashin's raincoat designs for Siggy Coat Company and Mainstreet Rainwear., 1950 - 1953; 13 pages (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's sketchbook of "Barnstormer" outerwear designs for Mainstreet., 1952; 1 volume (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Harris Raincoat Co. / March and Mendl, ca. 1952 - 1957; 2 oversize boxes and 1 folder
    This subseries contains Bonnie Cashin's illustrations of rainwear designed for Harris Raincoat Co., dba March and Mendl. Ancillary material includes swatches, original order form, memos, and photographs of Cashin's designs. All illustrations and writings by Bonnie Cashin contained in this subseries are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
    - Memos, sketches, and photographs regarding Cashin's rainwear designs for Harris Raincoat Company., 1955-1957; 21 pages (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Swatches used for Cashin's rainwear designs., ca. 1952 - 1955; 4 swatches (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's illustrations of coat designs for Lou Ritchie., April 7 - October 1955; 7 illustrations (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's illustrations of coat designs., ca. 1955; 10 illustrations (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's illustrations of coat designs for March and Mendl, a division of Harris Raincoat Co., ca. 1955; 22 illustrations (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's illustrations of coat designs for March and Mendl, a division of Harris Raincoat Co., ca. 1955; 27 illustrations (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Cashin's illustrations of coat designs., ca. 1955; 34 illustrations (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Cashin's pencil illustrations of rainwear designs, including hats., ca. 1955; 18 illustrations (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - "Rainpuff" coat design order form., 1956; 1 page (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Cashin's illustrations of children's outerwear designs., ca. 1955; 4 illustrations (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Cashin's illustrations of coat designs for Siggy., ca. 1955; 19 illustrations (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's illustrations of coat designs for Siggy., ca. 1955; 14 illustrations (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's illustrations of coat designs., ca. 1955; 8 illustrations (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Cashin's illustrations of coat designs., ca. 1955; 11 illustrations (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Modelia, 1963; 4 folders
    This subseries contains documentation of Bonnie Cashin's rainwear designs for manufacturer Modelia. This subseries primarily consists of Cashin's essays and other promotional material for the collection. All writings by Bonnie Cashin contained in this subseries are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
    - Collection essays and announcements for Cashin's "Rainy Day Clothes" designed for Modelia, Inc. Folder 1 of 3., 1963; 11 pages (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Collection essays for Cashin's "Rainy Day Clothes" designed for Modelia. Folder 2 of 3., 1963; 84 pages (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Collection essays for Cashin's "Rainy Day Clothes" designed for Modelia. Folder 3 of 3., 1963; 37 pages (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Line list for Cashin's rainwear collection., ca. 1963; 3 pages (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Ford Foundation Research Trip to India, 1956 - 1957; 3 oversize boxes and 2 folders
  This series documents Bonnie Cashin's Ford Foundation-sponsored trip to India to study textiles for export. The series includes detailed information regarding her business contacts, itineraries, research, and published conclusions. Some materials contained in this series are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
  - Clippings and Documents Regarding Travel (Ford Foundation), 1953 - 1968; 16 folders
    - Documents regarding Cashin's inclusion in Ford Foundation trip to evaluate Indian textiles for export., April 19, 1956 - October 9, 1956; 19 pages; 1 booklet (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Travel and shipping documents regarding Cashin's trip to India., October 10, 1956 - July 8, 1957; 61 pages (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Tourist brochures and maps collected by Cashin in India and Asia., ca. 1956 - 1975; 6 items (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Cashin's bills for hotel stays and souvenir purchases in India and Asia., October - December, 1956; 74 pages (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Personal and professional contact information collected by Cashin in India and Asia., ca. 1956; 23 pages; 43 business cards (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Personal and professional correspondence regarding Cashin's work in India and Asia., June 11, 1956 -December 21, 1957; 58 pages (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - "Report on Development of India's Handloom Fabrics for Export to the United States of America" by The Handloom Fabrics Survery Team Invited by the Government of India with the Cooperation of The Ford Foundation" and related documents., November 26, 1956 - September 30, 1957; 40 pages; 1 folder; 3 booklets (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding follow-up to Ford Foundation trip to India., September 30, 1957 - september 5, 1968; 52 pages (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Government-published booklets regarding handlooming and related industries in India., 1953 - 1955; 5 booklets (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Government-published booklets regarding handlooming and related industries in india., 1955 - 1961; 4 booklets (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Documents regarding Indian textiles, manufacture, and export., ca. 1956; 30 pages (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Travel itineraries for handloom textile survey team., October - November 1956; 9 pages (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Descriptions of research team objectives, background information on textile manufacturers, and types of materials., 1956; 31 pages (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Documents regarding India's handloom textiles in North America., December 1956 - November 27, 1958; 10 pages (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Copy of "the Illustrated Weekly of India.", November 4, 1956; 1 volume (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Clippings from Indian newspapers., 1956 - 1957; 51 pages (Box 294, Folder 1)
  - Design Ideas for Export Market, 1956 - 1957; 1 folder
    This subseries contains Bonnie Cashin's design illustrations of accessories constructed from Indian materials for export to Western markets. All materials contained in this subseries are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
    - Cashin's illustrations of accessory and clothing designs using materials exported from India., 1956 - 1957; 21 illustrations (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Journalistic Coverage of Bonnie Cashin, ca. 1937 - 2004; 45 oversize boxes and five folders (200 folders total)
  This series contains editorial coverage of Bonnie Cashin's design career. The series is particularly rich in published editorial coverage collected in a series of 20 clippings books and loose clippings. The series also includes photographs, proof sheets, and slides of Cashin and transcribed and recorded interviews with Cashin. The series is subdivided by press books and unbound clippings; editorial photographs of Cashin's designs; editorial drawings of Cashin's designs; publishing; recorded and transcribed interviews with Cashin; slides; Bonnie Cashin's interiors; press events.
  - Press Events (Journalistic Coverage)
    - Black and white photographs of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Adler and Adler and Sills and Co. modeled at various fashion shows., ca. 1951 - 1956; 20 photographs; 19 negatives; 1 CD (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Slides (Journalistic Coverage), ca. 1955 - 1980; 11 folders
    - Editorial photographs of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs., ca. 1955 - 1980; 22 slides (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co. featured in "Sports Illustrated.", 1963; 7 slides (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Publicity photoshoot of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., February 1970; 11 slides (Box 131, Folder 21)
    - Publicity photoshoot of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., March 1970 and undated; 16 slides (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - Publicity photoshoot of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., June 1970; 25 slides (Box 131, Folder 25)
    - Publicity photoshoot of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., December 1970 (Summer 1971 Collection); 27 slides (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Publicity photoshoots of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., November 1971 (Spring 1972 Collection); 24 slides (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Publicity photoshoot of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., June 1972 (Fall 1972 Collection); 52 slides (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Publicity photoshoot of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., September 1972 (Fall 1972 Collection); 51 slides (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Publicity photoshoot of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co. modeled at Cashin's apartment., ca. 1973; 9 slides (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Publicity photoshoot of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., May 1974 (Spring 1974 Collection); 15 slides (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Bonnie Cashin's Interiors (Journalistic Coverage), ca. 1939 - 2001; 6 folders
    This subseries contains photographs and magazine tear sheets featuring Bonnie Cashin's residential interiors. Some materials contained in this subseries are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
    - Magazine tear sheet of Cashin at home., ca. 1939; 1 page (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Tear sheets of Cashin's home featured in "House Beautiful," Volume 4, No. 2., Fall - Winter 1955 - 1956; 6 pages (double-sided) (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - Tear sheets of Cashin's home featured in "McCall's Magazine.", July 1962; 16 pages (double-sided) (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - Tear sheets of Cashin's home featured in "House and Garden.", July 1969; 17 pages (double-sided); 1 magazine (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - Tear sheets of Cashin's home featured in "The New York Times Magazine.", April 15, 1984; 3 pages; 1 magazine (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Cashin's home and posthumous article regarding Cashin's work featured in "The New York Times Magazine" written by Stephanie Day Iverson., March 2001; 1 magazine (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - Editorial Drawings of Cashin's Designs, ca. 1955 - 1968; 4 folders
    This subseries contains drawings of Bonnie Cashin's clothing designs for use in newspapers and magazines. The illustrations are not by Cashin.
    - Editorial drawings of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs (not drawn by Cashin)., ca. 1960s; 9 drawings (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - Oversize reprint of Cashin spread in Vogue., ca. 1968; 1 item (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Editorial drawings of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for newspaper (not drawn by Cashin)., ca. 1965; 3 drawings (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Editorial drawings of Cashin's ready-to-wear work for Dorian-Macsoud, Sills and Co., and Ballantyne., ca. 1955 - 1965; 4 drawings (Box 278, Folder 6)
  - Editorial Photographs of Cashin Designs, ca. 1950 - 1977; 6 oversize boxes and 5 folders
    This subseries contains editorial photographs and reprints of magazine spreads featuring Bonnie Cashin's designs. Some materials contained in this subseries are protected by United States copyright law and may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast without the prior written permission of The Bonnie Cashin Foundation.
    - Photographs of Cashin's ready-to-wear designs for Sills and Co., published in "Vogue.", September 1970; 8 photographs (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Oversized reprints of models wearing Cashin's fashion designs., 1950 - 1952; 20 photographs (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., Ca. 1950; 12 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Harper's Bazaar., Ca. 1950; 2 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Vogue., Ca. 1950; 19 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published as cover of Vogue., December 1952; 20 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, photo by Cecil Beaton, published in Vogue., Ca. 1950; 18 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, photo by Cecil Beaton, published in Vogue., Ca. 1950; 17 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, variation of this photo published., January - February 1950; 16 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, Ca. 1950; 13 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., Ca. 1950; 10 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, variation of this photo published in Park East., April 1950; 9 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., 1950; 8 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., Ca. 1950; 7 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Harper's Bazaar., 1950; 5 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Park East., 1950; 4 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Harper's Bazaar., Ca. 1950; 1 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Harper's Bazaar., September 1950; 3 items. (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - Oversized reprints of models wearing Cashin's fashion designs., 1953 - 1957; 17 photographs (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., Fall 1952; 10 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., Published Fall 1952 - Spring 1953; 11 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Milwaukee Journal and others., July 28, 1957; 13 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., Ca. 1955; 17 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., Ca. 1954; 16 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., Ca. 1953-1954; 15 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., Ca. 1953-1954; 14 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., July 1953; 6 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Vogue., February 1, 1954; 7 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published as advertisement., 1952; 5 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., 1950s; 4 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Mademoiselle., October 1953; 3 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Mademoiselle., October 1953; 2 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Vogue., August 15, 1953; 1 items. (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - Oversized reprints of models wearing Cashin's fashion designs for Dorian-Macsoud., 1958; 7 photographs (Box 273, Folder 3)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., 1958; 6 items. (Box 273, Folder 3)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., 1958; 7 items. (Box 273, Folder 3)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., 1958; 5 items. (Box 273, Folder 3)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., 1958; 4 items. (Box 273, Folder 3)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., 1958; 2 items. (Box 273, Folder 3)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., 1958; 1 items. (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - Oversized reprints of models wearing Cashin's fashion designs, photographed at her home in Briaricliff Manor., 1956; 2 photographs (Box 273, Folder 4)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Milwaukee Journal and others., July 28, 1957; 2 items. (Box 273, Folder 4)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Milwaukee Journal and others., July 28, 1957; 1 items. (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - Oversized reprints of models wearing Cashin's fashion designs., 1955-1963; 21 photographs (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in the New York Times., July 29, 1956; 4 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, variation of this photo published in Harper's Bazaar., 1960; 13 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., 1963; 21 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, variation of this photo published., 1963; 20 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., Ca. 1957; 19 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., Ca. 1957; 18 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., December 28, 1957; 17 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., Ca. 1957; 15 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., Ca. 1961; 12 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published, Ca. 1957; 9 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., Ca. 1955; 7 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., Ca. 1958; 5 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in New York Journal American., October 16, 1960; 3 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., Ca. 1955; 2 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in the New York Times Magazine., July 13, 1958; 1 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Harper's Bazaar, November 1957; 6 items. (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - Oversized reprints of models wearing Cashin's fashion designs., 1957-1964; 14 photographs (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in the reporter Dispatch and others., October 14, 1964; 13 items. (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Sports Illustrated., March 7, 1960; 14 items. (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in the Reporter Dispatch and others., October 14, 1964; 12 items. (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., 1958; 11 items. (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Harper's Bazaar., September 1958; 10 items. (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in New York Herald Tribune., September 23, 1959; 9 items. (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble., Ca. 1960; 7 items. (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., 1957; 5 items. (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Sports Illustrated., June 9, 1958; 4 items. (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, variation of this photo published in Detroit News Pictorial Magazine., February 9, 1958; 3 items. (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in New York Herald Tribune., September 23, 1959; 8 items. (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published., December 29, 1957; 2 items. (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Model in Cashin ensemble, published in Vogue., August 1958; 15 items. (Box 274, Folder 2)